Based on a True Story
Outback is a thriller, western film directed by Mike Green.
A young American couple’s Australian holiday takes a
terrifying turn when they get lost in the outback.
With only one another to rely on, the two are driven to extremes in order
to stay alive in the harsh and unforgiving wilderness.
Lisa Sachs, played by Lauren Lofberg.
Wade Kelly, played by Taylor Wiese.
Keith Coopers, played by Brendan Donoghue.
Cattle Musterer, played by Kym Cramp.
Cab Driver, played by Jim Winton Porter.
Back to the Outback is a 2021 animated family film that follows a group of misunderstood
Australian animals who escape from the zoo to find acceptance and freedom in the Outback.
It is directed by Clare Knight and Harry Cripps (in their feature directorial debuts), from
a screenplay written by Cripps, and a story by Cripps and Gregory Lessans.
The voice cast includes Isla Fisher, Tim Minchin, Eric Bana, Guy Pearce, Miranda Tapsell, Angus
Imrie, Keith Urban, and Jacki Weaver, and is distributed by Netflix Animation.
The film had a limited theatrical release on December 3, 2021, prior to streaming on Netflix
on December 10, to a generally positive reception from critics and audiences.
The film explores themes of australia, vacation, struggle for
survival, australian outback, lost in the desert.
The tone is intense.